{
  "topics": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "topic": "Oscars 2015",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "The award for best original screenplay went to which film",
          "correctAnswer": "Birdman",
          "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Boyhood",
            "Foxcatcher",
            "The Grand Budapest Hotel"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Despite 6 nominations, American Sniper picked up just one award. In which category?",
          "correctAnswer": "Best Sound Editing",
          "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Best Adapted Screenplay",
            "Best Visual Effects",
            "Best Hair and Makeup"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Julianne Moore won Best Actress for her depiction of what medical condition?",
          "correctAnswer": "Alzheimers",
          "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Leukemia",
            "Bi-polar disorder",
            "Parkinsons disease"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "During the ceremony, Lady Gaga performed songs from which classic musical?",
          "correctAnswer": "The Sound Of Music",
          "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Chicago",
            "Bugsy Malone",
            "Frozen"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Host, Neil Patrick Harris, surprised the audience with what noteworthy outfit?",
          "correctAnswer": "Just his underpants",
          "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A backless dress",
            "A rabbit onesey",
            "Medical Scrubs"
          ]
        }
      ],
      "relatedTopics": [
        2,
        4,
        7
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "topic": "Immigration",
      "synopsis": "Net migration to the UK is higher than when the coalition took office, shattering prime minister David Cameron’s ‘no ifs, no buts’ promise to cut the number. Learn more…",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "In April 2011, what did David Cameron promise his government would reduce net migration to?",
          "correctAnswer": "In the order of tens of thousands each year",
          "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Zero, absolute zero",
            "Less than 200,000",
            "An acceptable level"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "What was net migration to the UK in 2014?",
          "correctAnswer": "298,000",
          "incorrectAnswers": [
            "404,000",
            "155,000",
            "1.4 million"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Nigel Farage says UKIP would ban immigrants from entering the UK without what?",
          "correctAnswer": "Health Insurance",
          "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A passport",
            "A job",
            "£20,000 savings"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "According to the ONS what is the biggest reason for net migration to the UK?",
          "correctAnswer": "Formal Education",
          "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Joining family",
            "Seeking work",
            "Claiming benefits"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Channels 4s new documentary series, Immigration Street, is set on which road?",
          "correctAnswer": "Derby Road",
          "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Romania Street",
            "Whites Avenue",
            "London Crescent"
          ],
          "relatedTopics": [
            2,
            4,
            7
          ]
        }
      ],
      "relatedTopics": [
        2,
        4,
        7
      ]
    },
    {
          "id": 1,
          "topic": "Greek Bailout",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question": "The award for best original screenplay went to which film",
              "correctAnswer": "Birdman",
              "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Boyhood",
                "Foxcatcher",
                "The Grand Budapest Hotel"
              ]
            },
            {
              "question": "Despite 6 nominations, American Sniper picked up just one award. In which category?",
              "correctAnswer": "Best Sound Editing",
              "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Best Adapted Screenplay",
                "Best Visual Effects",
                "Best Hair and Makeup"
              ]
            },
            {
              "question": "Julianne Moore won Best Actress for her depiction of what medical condition?",
              "correctAnswer": "Alzheimers",
              "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Leukemia",
                "Bi-polar disorder",
                "Parkinsons disease"
              ]
            },
            {
              "question": "During the ceremony, Lady Gaga performed songs from which classic musical?",
              "correctAnswer": "The Sound Of Music",
              "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Chicago",
                "Bugsy Malone",
                "Frozen"
              ]
            },
            {
              "question": "Host, Neil Patrick Harris, surprised the audience with what noteworthy outfit?",
              "correctAnswer": "Just his underpants",
              "incorrectAnswers": [
                "A backless dress",
                "A rabbit onesey",
                "Medical Scrubs"
              ]
            }
          ],
          "relatedTopics": [
            2,
            4,
            7
          ]
        },
        {
              "id": 1,
              "topic": "Champions League",
              "questions": [
                {
                  "question": "The award for best original screenplay went to which film",
                  "correctAnswer": "Birdman",
                  "incorrectAnswers": [
                    "Boyhood",
                    "Foxcatcher",
                    "The Grand Budapest Hotel"
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "question": "Despite 6 nominations, American Sniper picked up just one award. In which category?",
                  "correctAnswer": "Best Sound Editing",
                  "incorrectAnswers": [
                    "Best Adapted Screenplay",
                    "Best Visual Effects",
                    "Best Hair and Makeup"
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "question": "Julianne Moore won Best Actress for her depiction of what medical condition?",
                  "correctAnswer": "Alzheimers",
                  "incorrectAnswers": [
                    "Leukemia",
                    "Bi-polar disorder",
                    "Parkinsons disease"
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "question": "During the ceremony, Lady Gaga performed songs from which classic musical?",
                  "correctAnswer": "The Sound Of Music",
                  "incorrectAnswers": [
                    "Chicago",
                    "Bugsy Malone",
                    "Frozen"
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "question": "Host, Neil Patrick Harris, surprised the audience with what noteworthy outfit?",
                  "correctAnswer": "Just his underpants",
                  "incorrectAnswers": [
                    "A backless dress",
                    "A rabbit onesey",
                    "Medical Scrubs"
                  ]
                }
              ],
              "relatedTopics": [
                2,
                4,
                7
              ]
            },
            {
                  "id": 1,
                  "topic": "Islamic State (Isis)",
                  "questions": [
                    {
                      "question": "The award for best original screenplay went to which film",
                      "correctAnswer": "Birdman",
                      "incorrectAnswers": [
                        "Boyhood",
                        "Foxcatcher",
                        "The Grand Budapest Hotel"
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "question": "Despite 6 nominations, American Sniper picked up just one award. In which category?",
                      "correctAnswer": "Best Sound Editing",
                      "incorrectAnswers": [
                        "Best Adapted Screenplay",
                        "Best Visual Effects",
                        "Best Hair and Makeup"
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "question": "Julianne Moore won Best Actress for her depiction of what medical condition?",
                      "correctAnswer": "Alzheimers",
                      "incorrectAnswers": [
                        "Leukemia",
                        "Bi-polar disorder",
                        "Parkinsons disease"
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "question": "During the ceremony, Lady Gaga performed songs from which classic musical?",
                      "correctAnswer": "The Sound Of Music",
                      "incorrectAnswers": [
                        "Chicago",
                        "Bugsy Malone",
                        "Frozen"
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "question": "Host, Neil Patrick Harris, surprised the audience with what noteworthy outfit?",
                      "correctAnswer": "Just his underpants",
                      "incorrectAnswers": [
                        "A backless dress",
                        "A rabbit onesey",
                        "Medical Scrubs"
                      ]
                    }
                  ],
                  "relatedTopics": [
                    2,
                    4,
                    7
                  ]
                }
  ]
}